...like you're 9 years old?
(Howard:)-You live with your mother?
-No. That's the sad part.
(Howard:)Rough. Okay, check this out.
(Howard:)My mother made me wear rubber gloves
to kindergarten...
(Howard:)...so I wouldn't pick up a disease
from the other children.
(Bernadette:)That's nothing.
I couldn't ride a bicycle...
...because my mother was afraid
I'd hit a bump and lose my virginity.
(Howard:)Oh, wow, you didn't, did you?
(Bernadette:)Not on a bicycle. In a Camry.
A Corolla.
[BOTH CHUCKLE]
(Howard:)-More wine?
-I'd love some.
(Howard:)Listen, you have to come
to Shabbat dinner at my house sometime.
(Leonard:)Why?
(Howard:)A Catholic girl like you
wearing a big cross like that...
(Howard:)...might just give my mother the big
brain aneurysm I've been hoping for.
(Bernadette:)Okay, but only if you come to Sunday
dinner at my house wearing a yarmulke.
(Howard:)It's a date.